(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you so much
溢れるこの愛きっともう止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop anymore
あいあいあい あいにじゅー
Ai-ai-ai, I Need You
もっともっと 好きになってね
Please love me more and more
君のことだいすき
I love you so much
だいすき
I love you
溢れるこの (愛は) きっと (ずっと) も止まらない
This overflowing (love) is sure (always) never to stop
(Foo!)
あいあいあいあいあいらぶゆー
Ai Ai Ai Ai Ai Love You
君があいあ
I love you
あいあいあいあい♡あいらぶゆー
Ai Ai Ai Ai ♡ Ai Love You
アニメにハマって
I got hooked on anime,
歌いたくなっちゃった
And now I want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら
While watching my favorite scenes,
カラオケ歌えるなんて...
Being able to sing karaoke...
尊すぎてツラいっ！
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Find the song you want to sing!
どアニメ宣言！
Do Anime Sengen!
JOYSOUND
吉野家でごはんでしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya♪
ぎゅうっ
Beef!
ぎゅう
ぎゅうぎゅう
Beef, beef!
ぎゅううう〜
Beeeeeeef!
うま！
Delicious!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Savor the true passion of the original.
牛丼は吉野家
Beef bowl is Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれな！
This is definitely it!
せーの！
Ready, set...!
こんばんは！
Good evening!
ホロライブ3期生ライブ
Hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦
Operation Kyururun:
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
The Ultimate Idols, You Have To Stan!
にご来場いただき
Thank you for coming to
誠にありがとうございます！
thank you very much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
To ensure you enjoy the live show until the end...
いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
...we have a few announcements for you.
公演中の撮影、録音、
Photography, recording, and the use...
録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
...of recording equipment are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
The venue is non-smoking.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell...
無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
...don't overexert yourself and inform the staff.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、
Moshing, diving, and...
ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
...throwing objects onto the stage...
他のみんなの迷惑になったり、
...or any actions that bother others...
公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
...or interfere with the show are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
おー！
YEAH!
また、本公演は映像配信及び
Additionally, cameras for video streaming...
写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
...and photography are in use, and you may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに
These videos and photos may be used...
使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
...for promotional purposes. We appreciate your understanding.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは、
Also, the hashtag for the live show is...
＃きゅるるん大作戦DAY1です。
#KyururunDaisakusenDay1.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
We'd love it if you'd post using the hashtag!
それでは、開演までもう少しです。
Well then, it's just a little longer until the start.
みんなの声をたくさん聞かせてぺこ！
Let me hear your voices, peko!
それじゃあ、3期生、エンジン行くか！
Alright, 3rd Gen, let's do our huddle!
みんな、今からマイクがなくなるので、
Everyone, the microphones will be off now...
静かに、静かに。
...so be quiet, be quiet.
I-I-I-I-I love you　も
I-I-I-I-I love you and
I-I-I-I-I need you
もっと　もっと　もっと
More, more, more,
好きなだけ愛させて
let me love you as much as I want.
さいこーのライブ、いくぺこー！
The best live, let's go peko!
みんなでさいこーの思い出つくろーね！
Let's make the best memories together!
ズルルのない　君だらけ
Full of you, with no cheating,
溶かしてるわ　私
I'm melting away.
心臓ドキドキ　なってる
My heart is pounding.
OK? How about?
OK? How about it?
毎日　幻覚あらわれて
Hallucinations appear every day,
頭に　花咲いちゃって
and flowers bloom in my head.
恋ってやつは　非日常ですわ
This thing called love is extraordinary.
いっそ　食べちゃいたい
I'd rather just eat you up,
フリーズした　感情
these frozen emotions...
誰もが持ってる　お願い
The wish everyone has.
純純　萌萌っしょ
Pure, pure, moe, moe, right?
ドバっと　急上昇
Surging up all at once.
これが恋なら　もう後悔しないわ
If this is love, I won't regret it anymore.
だから　君のこと
So, it's you that I...
大好き大好き大好き大好き　大好き
love, love, love, love, I love you!
溢れる　この愛は　きっと　ずっと　止まらない
This overflowing love surely will never stop.
I-I-I-I-I love you　君が
I-I-I-I-I love you, because
I-I-I-I-I need you
もっと　もっと　もっと
More, more, more,
好きなだけ愛させて
let me love you as much as I want.
揺れるハートが　ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My shaking heart goes boing boing boing,
穴に落ちて　あびゃびゃびゃ
falling into a hole and going abya-bya-bya.
こんなになっても　いまだ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't get out.
どうしたもんかね　ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui-nui-nui.
助けて君たち　あほーいほーい
Save me, you guys! Ahoy-hoy!
もっと　もっと　もっと
More, more, more,
好きなだけ愛してね
love me as much as you want.
フワフワ　夢のなか
Fluffy, inside a dream,
君の声で　目が覚めた
I woke up to your voice.
五感ぜんぶが　君のシグナル
All my five senses are your signals.
毎度　お騒がせごめん
Sorry for the disturbance every time,
キュンで　壊れちゃいそう
I feel like I'll break from the heart-throbs.
恋ってやつは　制御不能ですわ
This thing called love is uncontrollable.
いっそ　抱きしめて
I'd rather you just hug me,
壊しても　いいよ
it's okay if you break me.
誰にも邪魔は　させない
I won't let anyone get in the way.
ピチピチ　感情で
With fresh, lively emotions,
キラキラ　急展開
sparkling, sudden developments.
これが運命なら　もう迷わないわ
If this is fate, I won't hesitate anymore.
覚悟してね　君だけが
Get ready, because I love you alone,
大好き大好き大好き大好き　大好き
love you, love you, love you, I love you!
私の　この愛は　じっと　ずっと　離さない
This love of mine will never, ever let go.
B-B-B-B-B My Baby　そして
B-B-B-B-B My Baby, and then
K-K-K-K-K Kiss Me
もっと　もっと　もっと
More, more, more,
私だけを見ててね
please only look at me.
むしろ誰も泣いちゃうかもね
Actually, everyone might end up crying
だってそんなのって無いペコじゃん
Because that's just not right, peko!
わかってるよね ダーリン
You know that, right, darling?
いっぱい愛をましまし
Give me lots and lots of love!
ノエル もっと!
Noel, more!
ぺこら もっと!
Pekora, more!
フレア もっと!
Flare, more!
マリン もっと!
Marine, more!
ホロライブファンタジーを 愛してるー!
We love Hololive Fantasy!
君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
溢れるこの愛は きっと ずっと 鳴り止まない
This overflowing love will surely never stop ringing!
I I I I love you 君が I I I I need you
I I I I love you, you are the one I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと 君だけ愛させて
Let me love only you more, more, more, more!
ときめくハートが ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My heart is throbbing, thumping...
矢に射抜かれて あびゃびゃびゃ
pierced by an arrow, I'm all flustered!
こんなになったら 魔法は解けません
Now that it's come to this, the magic won't wear off!
本気になってる ぬいのいぬい
I'm getting serious...
行き着く先まで あほいほい
To the very end!
もっと もっと もっと もっと 好きなだけ愛してね
Love me more, more, more, more, as much as you like!
I I I I love you
I I I I need you
私たちの愛をもっと
Give us even more of your love!
叫べ愛のコール!
Shout out the call of love!
あ、ピチピチ あほい! 美少女あほい! お色気担当のマリンです!
Ah, fresh and lively, Ahoy! A beautiful girl, Ahoy! I'm the sexy one, Marine!
踊る阿呆に見る阿呆
Dancing fools and watching fools...
共に脱落組に加わりましょう
let's join the dropouts together!
面舵いっぱい! 全速前進だあ!
Hard to starboard! Full speed ahead!
うさぎ同盟 最強女神 ぺこらペコら!
Rabbit Alliance, the strongest goddess, Pekora-peko-ra!
まんまる よしよしして
Embrace me in a circle and say 'good girl'...
爆速 横取りめちゃ 横取りだ
taking a shortcut at top speed!
エルフレ!
Elfre!
うさぎか?
A rabbit?
大成功のため
For a huge success!
初見コールも いけちゃう?
Can you handle the first-time call too?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
自画自賛 震撼 コール
Self-praising, shocking call!
お決まりの ファンサです
It's the usual fan service...
大好き 溢れちゃう
my love is overflowing!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
極めた おたげ 踊れる
I've mastered the otage dancing!
新規もいる
There are newcomers...
古参いる
there are veterans...
もはや 贔屓なのだ ぶっちゃけ
honestly, I'm just biased now.
会いたい
I want to meet you...
推したい
I want to support you!
それなー!
That's right!
お決まりコールで!
With the usual call!
現場で テンプレ 応援
At the venue, with the standard support...
きゅるきゅる チアチア
kyuru kyuru cheer cheer!
ふれ ふれ エルフレ
Go go, Elfre!
褒められて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type that grows with praise!
左!
Left!
右!
Right!
世界で一番愛してる!
I love you most in the world!
今ならチャンネル登録なんて無料!
Right now, subscribing to the channel is free!
じょいじょい えんじょい
Joy joy, enjoy!
団長のノエルだぞー
I'm the leader Noel!
ゆるふわの騎士を お抱きしめよう
Let me embrace the fluffy knights!
中毒みたい
Like an addiction...
クラップでいいたい
I want to say it with a clap!
ぎゅっ!
Gyu!
どん!
Don!
いつも いつも 大感謝!
Always, always, big thanks!
お菓子より おいしい 今日を あげちゃう
I'll give you a day that's tastier than sweets!
実質 メンバー!
Virtually a member!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
ハートの 振り付けも コピる
Copy the heart choreography too!
可愛いとか 超えて好き
I love you beyond just 'cute'...
拗らせちゃう
it's getting complicated!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
概念 からも 集める
I'll gather you even from concepts!
ガチ勢も
Serious fans...
エンジョイ勢も
and casual fans...
もはや 全員 推し決定だ
you're all my favorites now!
ぶっちゃけ
Honestly...
見てたい 乗りたい
I want to watch, I want to ride!
それなー!
That's right!
現場で 全力 応援
At the venue, full-power support...
きゅるきゅる チアチア
kyuru kyuru cheer cheer!
みんなの王様ー!
Everyone's king!
みんなの歌姫ー!
Everyone's songstress!
みんなの団長ー!
Everyone's leader!
みんなの船長ー!
Everyone's captain!
ラブアンドピース どんな時も
Love and peace, no matter what!
推しが 凹んだ 時でも
Even when your favorite is feeling down!
トライアンドエラー 重ねたい
Try and error, I want to keep trying!
君と 見たい 景色があるんだ
There's a view I want to see with you!
っしゃーいくぞ!
Let's go!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
自画自賛 震撼 コール
Self-praising, shocking call!
お決まりの ファンサです
It's the usual fan service...
大好き 大好き 一生好きだよ
I love you, I love you, I'll love you forever!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
ラストまで おたげる
Otage-ing until the very end!
頑張る貴方 存在が
The hardworking you, your very existence...
最強 大優勝
is the strongest, the best!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル
Kyuru kyuru kyuru kyuru idol
永遠の 愛 誓い 合える
We can vow eternal love to each other!
推しいる
I have a favorite...
箱推しは
support the whole group...
もはや 生涯 オタク 決定だ
I'm a lifelong otaku now!
それなー!
That's right!
もうずっと
Forever...
and ever!
現場で 限界 応援
At the venue, to the limit support...
きゅるきゅる チア☆
kyuru kyuru cheer☆
チア！チア！
Cheer! Cheer!
チア！
Cheer!
ちょっと安心しすぎたー
We're a bit too relaxed!
落ち着こう、落ち着こう
Let's calm down, calm down.
落ち着いて、落ち着いて
Calm down, calm down.
落ち着くために自己紹介しよっか
Let's introduce ourselves to calm down.
自己紹介オッケー、そうだね
Self-intro, okay. Good idea.
じゃあ、ぺこらから行きますよ
Well then, Pekora will go first!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko!
ホロライブ3期生の
Hololive 3rd Gen's...
兎田ぺこらっ…
Usada Pekora...
お前、こんぺこって言わせてよ
Wait, let me say "Kon-peko".
言いたいよね、確かに
You want to say it, right? True.
もう一回やってよ、もう一回
Do it again, one more time.
なんて言えばいいの、ぺこらはじゃあ
What should I say then, Pekora?
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこって言ったら
If I say "Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko"...
向こうも言いたいんだ、そういうことね
The audience wants to say it too. I see.
みんなやってくれますか？
Will everyone do it?
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Kon-peko, kon-peko, kon-peko!
いいね、いいね！
Nice, nice!
ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらっ…と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada Pekora... and!
はい、じゃあフレアは「こんぬい」じゃなくて「はいダーリン」って言うから「はいハニー」って返してくださーい
Okay, I'll say "Hi Darling" instead of "Kon-nui", so please reply "Hi Honey"!
あー、なるほどね
Ah, I see.
はいダーリン！
Hi Darling!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレア…と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shiranui Flare... and!
じゃあ団長は「牛丼は？」って言うんで「並盛り！」って言ってください
Alright, I'll say "Gyudon wa?", so please say "Namimori!".
牛丼ね、万能、万能だから
Gyudon, it's universal, universal.
牛丼はー？
Gyudon wa—?
あ、イェーイ！そうだよね！
Ah, yay! That's right!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエル…と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel... and!
君たち、今もしやフレアのこと「ハニー」って言った？
You guys, did you just call Flare "Honey"?
言ったー！お前らー！
We did! You guys!
よろよろ、よろよろ…
Wobble, wobble...
何だお前？大丈夫か？
Who are you? Are you okay?
マリンのこと捨ててしまったの？君たち
Did you guys just abandon Marine?
なんちゃって
Just kidding!
じゃあ普通に「あほーい」で行きますんで「あほーい」って言ってくださいね
I'll just go with "Ahoi", so please say "Ahoi" back!
あほーい！
Ahoi!
誰があほや！
Who are you calling an idiot?!
なんちゃって。えー、ホロライブ…
Just kidding. Uh, Hololive...
3期生…えっと、ど忘れしちゃった。ホロライブ3期生
3rd Gen... Uh, I forgot. Hololive 3rd Gen...
宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine-desu!
いいねー！イェーイ！
Nice! Yay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
せっかくさ、みんななんかアイドル口上みたいなのさ
Since we're here, let's do those idol introductions...
ぶっ放したやつをやる？やろうやろう
Should we do the ones we practiced? Let's do it!
これやるしかないって、配信でまたね
We have to do this, like we did in the stream.
じゃあ順番で。順番で行きましょう、順番で
Let's go in order then. In order.
みんな覚えてるよね？ぺこらの口上
Everyone remembers, right? Pekora's intro.
絶対覚えてねーぞ、お前ら
I bet they don't remember it at all!
覚えてるよね？ちゃんと。覚えてる人手挙げて！
You remember, right? Raise your hand if you do!
あ、結構上がってる。すごい！
Ah, quite a few hands. Amazing!
全然覚えてねーって、どっちやねん
"I don't remember at all," you say? Which is it?!
じゃあ今から覚えてくださいね、じゃあぺこらから行きますよ
Then please learn it now. Pekora will start!
ラビット、キャロット、きらっと登場！
Rabbit, Carrot, sparkling appearance!
最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこ！
The strongest idol Pekora is here-peko!
まだまだ続くよ、ぺこらストーリー！
It's not over yet, the Pekora story!
ちょっとフレアめっちゃ難しいんだけどさ、いけるかなこれ
Flare's is super hard, though. Can we do it?
いけるいける！みんなもあの掛け声、大丈夫だよ
You can do it! Everyone knows the call, it's fine.
これみんなにもコールアンドレスポンスして欲しくて、あの、「準備は？」って言ったら「万端！」
I want everyone to do the call-and-response. When I say "Are you ready?", say "Ready!"
「コールは？」って聞くので「簡単！」って言ってください
I'll ask "How's the call?", so please say "Simple!"
手拍子パンパン！ステップトントン！
Clap clap! Step step!
ステップ簡単！私は？
Step's simple! And I am?
フレア！めっちゃ難しいだろこれ
Flare! That's super hard, right?
めっちゃ、これ練習ね
Seriously. This is practice.
覚えてください。では行きますよ
Please remember it. Here we go!
こんぬい！準備は？
Kon-nui! Are you ready?
万端！コールは？
Ready! How's the call?
簡単！手拍子パンパン！
Simple! Clap clap!
ステップ簡単！私は？
Step's simple! And I am?
フレア！
Flare!
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Shiranui Flare-desu!
じゃあ次はノエル行きます。団長コールアンドレスポンスないからちょっとラップします
Then next is Noel. Since I don't have a call-and-response, I'll rap a bit.
こっから行こうかな、行きます！
I'll start from here. Let's go!
目指せ申し子の食べ物、答えは牛丼
The child's go-to food, the answer is Gyudon.
おろしで飲み物、みんなの胸キュン
Grated is a drink, making everyone's heart throb.
ダメダメ、中毒。ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエル！
No way, it's addictive. Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel!
えー、マリンは恒例なんですが先に予習しましょうか。
Um, for Marine it's a regular thing, but let's practice beforehand.
マリンが「マリンはー？」って言ったら「船長ー！」で、
When I say "Marine is...?", you shout "Captain!"
マリンが「君たちはー？」で「一味ー！」、
When I say "And you guys are...?", shout "Crew!"
我ら無敵の「海賊団！」
We are the invincible "Pirate Crew!"
で最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長宝鐘マリンです！」って言うから、
And finally, I'll say "Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!"
そしたら問答無用で「カワイイー！」って言う。
Then, shout "Cute!" without question.
わかりましたね？
Understood?
まあ余裕だよね！
It's easy!
ナイスな返事できて、まる！じゃあ行きますよー！
Great response, perfect! Here we go!
マリンはー？
Marine is...?
船長ー！
Captain!
君たちはー？
And you guys are...?
一味ー！
Crew!
我ら無敵のー？
We are the invincible...?
海賊団！
Pirate Crew!
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!
カワイイー！
Cute!
いやー気持ちいいですねこれ。
Man, that feels good.
そんな可愛いって… 良かったなー可愛いいって言われて良かったなー。
To be called cute... I'm so glad, I'm so glad to be called cute.
そんなことないけど…。
Not really...
でもコールアンドレスポンスね、ちょっと一発目からもうすごい難しいのやらせちゃって、どうもすみませんね。
But the call and response, sorry for making you do such a hard one right from the start.
たくさんありがとうねー！声が聞こえますよー！
Thanks a lot! We can hear your voices!
さっきのさ、うちらの円陣聞こえました？
Did you hear our stage huddle just now?
聞こえたー！やったー！
We heard it! Yay!
ちょっとね、聞こえるかなーって不安だったんだよね。
I was a bit worried if you'd be able to hear it.
こっちにはね、君らの声よく聞こえるんだけど、さすがにマイク通さないとちっちゃかったかなと思って。
We can hear you well, but I thought our voices might be too small without the mics.
でもお腹から出した、お腹からね。
But we used our guts, our guts.
あ、聞こえた！ありがとう！聞こえるよ！
Oh, you heard it! Thank you! I hear you!
こっちにも声聞こえてますよ！
We can hear your voices too!
衣装のことも言わなきゃ！
We have to talk about the costumes!
そうだよ、そうだよ！一曲目から出ちゃいましたけど！
Right, right! We came out in them from the first song!
突然の新衣装、可愛いでしょ？
New costumes out of nowhere, cute right?
ちょっとずつ違うところがありますんで、これさ、よーっと見てね。
There are slight differences for each of us, so look closely.
ぺこらーは耳、羽がついているぺこです！
Pekora has wings on her ears-peko!
なんと考案者はノエルちゃん！
And the one who came up with it was Noel-chan!
そう、ノエル！すごいでしょ？
Yes, Noel! Isn't it great?
はい、お待たせしました。
Alright, thanks for waiting.
マリンはね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほらこんな感じで、バツバツバツバツバツ… ってなってて。
Marine has a headpiece, look, like this, with X-X-X-X-X patterns.
カワイイー！
Cute!
ノエルちゃんはなんかポンポン付いてます。
Noel-chan has these pom-poms.
フレアはこの頭のリボンかな。
For Flare, it's probably this ribbon on the head.
カワイイねー。靴下違いますよ、みんな。
Cute! Everyone's socks are different too.
フレアはギャルじゃないんで。
Flare isn't a gyaru, so...
うちらギャル！ぺこらもギャル！ギャルです！
We're gyaru! Pekora is a gyaru too! We're gyaru!
ちなみに皆さん、うちらね、結構めちゃめちゃ喋りすぎてるみたいで。
By the way everyone, it seems like we've been talking way too much.
ヤバイヤバイ！嘘でしょ！？
Oh no! You're kidding!
このまま音楽しないのかい、みたいな感じでスタッフさんに睨まれてますけれども。
The staff is giving us looks like, "Are you ever going to play music?"
配信で見てる方、概要欄に配信チケットのリンクありますので。
For those watching on stream, there's a link for tickets in the description.
ぜひあの、次の曲でちょっとチラ見せは終わりぺこなので。
The sneak peek ends after the next song-peko.
終わっちゃうので、今のうちに。
So it's ending soon, get them now.
まだ見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるんですよ！ぜひとも、お願いします！
There's still so much we want you to see! Please!
ハッシュタグ #きゅるるん大作戦DAY1 でいっぱい呟いてね！
Tweet a lot with the hashtag #KyururunDaisakusenDay1!
ていうか、その前に、これやらないと！生バンドがね、すごいカッコイイじゃない？
Wait, before that, we have to do this! The live band is so cool, right?
そうだねー！だからちょっと聞かせたくて。じゃあぺこらちゃんから行ってもらっていいですか？
True! I want you to hear them. Pekora-chan, could you start?
了解ぺこ！バンド、キーボード担当、うさだぺこら！
Roger-peko! The band's keyboardist, Usada Pekora!
すごーい！めちゃ弾いてる！
Amazing! He's really playing!
よし、行くよ！ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Alright, here I go! Guitar, Houshou Marine!
カッケー！カッコイイ！
So cool! Awesome!
はい！ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Yes! Drums, Shirogane Noel!
ヤバイ！カッコヨ！
Insane! So cool!
じゃあフレア、ベースやります！
Then Flare will do the bass!
カッコイイわー！最高！
That's so cool! The best!
最高！サンキュー！はい、うちらが演奏してます（嘘）。
Best! Thank you! Yes, we're the ones playing [lie].
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょうか！
Oh, let's head to the next song soon!
場所場所！場所場所！あ、こっちじゃない、あ、ここでね。
Positions! Positions! Oh, not here, ah, here.
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょう！
Okay, let's start the next song!
せーの、リアリティ・ファンタジー！
Ready, set, Reality Fantasy!
H-O-L-O-L-I-V-E
F-A-N-T-A-S-Y
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Departure! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
お宝探しに 大海原へと 出航だ
Off to the high seas to find treasure, we're setting sail.
冒険！出発！
Adventure! Departure!
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
身も心からもぴょんぴょん わくわく
Even from my heart, jump jump, heart pounding
頂点 じょーじょー
At the peak, jump jump!
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
水平線 向こう側
Horizontal lines, far beyond
新天地 待っててね
The new world is waiting, wait for me
運命 なんか飛び越して
Destiny, somehow, jumping over
その先へ
To what lies beyond
さあ！ Reality Fantasy
Ah, Reality, Fantasy
二つの狭間で
Between the two
夢歌え 超えたたかく一緒に
Dream, sing, soar high together
さあ！ まだ見ない
Ah, to a world that hasn't been seen yet
世界へと 君を連れてくよ
I'll take you along with me
みんなが繋がる物語が手に
The thing that connects everyone is in our hands
さあ始まるよ
Now it's starting
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
みんなの志抱いて
Everyone's heart's determination, hold it up!
あきらめない騎士団集合
Ah, yes, the Kishidan group is gathered!
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切って
Aiming at the sun in our hearts, cutting through the wind
さらに輝け
Shine even brighter
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
迷いと夢 晴天に
Glance and dream, at the zenith
掲げたら 突撃だ
If you hold it up, it's a surprise attack
よって立ち この旅見守って
Gather, protect this journey
さあ！ Reality Fantasy
Ah, Reality, Fantasy
二つの狭間で
Between the two
誇上げて 迎えUtopiaへ
Raise it up, and welcome it, to Utopia
さあ！ それぞれの
Ah, from each one's world
世界から 垣根を超えたら
If you cross the border
みんなが繋がる物語に
The thing that connects everyone is in our hands
さあ始まるよ
Now it's starting
明るく陽気に 新たみ乗り越え
Brightly, cheerfully, reform, ride over
ほーら ライブ！
HOLO! LIVE!
愛嬌解放 うさ耳すまして
Love's liberation, whisper in my ears
ほーら ライブ！
HOLO! LIVE!
騎士道と誇り 胸に刻んだら
Kishidan and pride, carved into our hearts
ほーら ライブ！
HOLO! LIVE!
神話に伝わる 神秘の囁き
Myths and legends, whispered secrets
ほーら ライブ！
HOLO! LIVE!
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
さあ！ Reality Fantasy
Ah, Reality, Fantasy
二つの狭間で
Between the two
夢歌え 超えたたかく一緒に
Dream, sing, soar high together
さあ！ まだ見ない
Ah, to a world that hasn't been seen yet
世界へと 君を連れてくよ
I'll take you along with me
準備はほら出来たよ
The preparation is done, look!
ルートも先回ったよ
The route has been taken over
みんなが繋がる物語に
The thing that connects everyone is in our hands
さあ始まるよ
Now it's starting
冒険！出発！ さあ！
Adventure! Depart! Now!
挑戦！開始！ さあ！
Challenge! Start! Now!
時は2026年
The year is 2026.
2回目の3期生ライブ
The second 3rd Generation live.
このチャンスを逃してなるものか
I won't let this chance slip away!
今こそ全人類兎化計画を
Now is the time for the Project...
遂行する！
...Whole Human Rabbit-ification!